export const sections = [
  {
    title: "Pastoral Ministry",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "The ministry of the Pastor is most relevant to:",
        options: ["Teaching Centre", "Local Church", "Mission field"],
        answer: "Local Church",
      },
      {
        question:
          "God is building strong local churches and He wants members of the Local church to flow in the Spirit.",
        options: ["True", "False", "None of the above"],
        answer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The following names are used to refer to a Pastor and his functions in the New Testament except:",
        options: ["Shepherd", "Overseer", "Brother"],
        answer: "Brother",
      },
      {
        question: "The major function of a Pastor is to:",
        options: [
          "Feed the flock",
          "Dictate to the flock",
          "Dominate the flock",
        ],
        answer: "Feed the flock",
      },
      {
        question:
          "There is no substitute for the Local Church, every believer should settle in and get involved.",
        options: ["True", "False", "None of the above"],
        answer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The ministry of Help is supernaturally associated with the ministry of:",
        options: ["Apostle", "Pastor", "Prophets"],
        answer: "Pastor",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The Local Church is a family and every believer should be a member of it.",
        options: ["False", "True", "None of the Above"],
        answer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "In the Local Church, there is no higher spiritual authority than the Pastor because he has the spiritual oversight of the Local Church.",
        options: ["Indifferent", "True", "False"],
        answer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The following are characteristics of good supportive ministry except:",
        options: ["Good Report", "Spiritual Maturity", "Divisive Tendencies"],
        answer: "Divisive Tendencies",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The Bishop must be blameless, apt to teach, and have one wife.",
        options: ["True", "False", "All of the above"],
        answer: "All of the above",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Businessmen can be Helpers or deacons, and very often their financial and business expertise can be a great assistance to the Pastor.",
        options: ["True", "False", "Surely Not"],
        answer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "A fellow in the Pastoral Ministry who is either not called to that office or who hurts and scatters the flock is called:",
        options: ["True Pastor", "Caring Pastor", "False Pastor"],
        answer: "False Pastor",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    title: "Great Commission",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "God wants all men to be saved and come to the knowledge of truth.",
        options: ["True", "False", "I don't know"],
        answer: "True",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the full meaning of UPG?",
        options: [
          "Under Promising Ground",
          "Unreached People Groups",
          "Unchurched People Groups",
        ],
        answer: "Unreached People Groups",
      },
      {
        question: "One major barrier of the great commission is:",
        options: ["Acceptance", "Availability", "Education"],
        answer: "Acceptance",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Ideally, people groups are always defined as a group of people that understand themselves well and are bound by cultural and traditional heritages.",
        options: ["False", "True", "Maybe"],
        answer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "According to Matthew 9:37-38, Jesus expects that every believer and Church will abound in praying for:",
        options: [
          "More Churches",
          "Financial Resources",
          "Labourers into the Harvest",
        ],
        answer: "Labourers into the Harvest",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The Great Commission is not an option to be considered; it is a command to be obeyed.",
        options: ["Maybe", "True", "False"],
        answer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "'The Spirit of Christ is the Spirit of missions. The nearer we get to Him, the more intensely missionary we become.' The above quote was made by:",
        options: ["Kenneth E. HAGIN", "Henry Martyn", "Matt Beemer"],
        answer: "Henry Martyn",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The following are the Biblical mediums by which the Gospel is made known except:",
        options: [
          "Preaching and Teaching",
          "Prayer and Power",
          "Debates and Oratory Prowess",
        ],
        answer: "Debates and Oratory Prowess",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Complete these lines with appropriate words according to Romans 10:4: Send, Preach, Hear, Believe ----- and ‚Äê------",
        options: ["See, Know", "Call, See", "Call, Saved"],
        answer: "Call, Saved",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Gracespring Christian Centre's Vision and Mission is simplified as:",
        options: [
          "Equipping the saints for Ministry",
          "Church Planting",
          "Impacting lives with the Gospel",
        ],
        answer: "Impacting lives with the Gospel",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The following manifestation of the Spirit will be frequent in the ministry of an evangelist except:",
        options: [
          "The Power gifts",
          "Gifts of Healings",
          "Profound Knowledge of the Word",
        ],
        answer: "Profound Knowledge of the Word",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Global Evangelization is a major instruction from the Lord Jesus Christ to be carried out by:",
        options: ["Apostles", "Believers", "Evangelists"],
        answer: "Believers",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    title: "Homiletics",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "The science and art of preaching, teaching, and communicating is known as:",
        options: ["Hermeneutics", "Homiletics", "Hermology"],
        answer: "Homiletics",
      },
      {
        question:
          "In the New Testament, the message or proclamation of the heralds of God or Christ is known as:",
        options: ["Teaching", "Preaching", "Exhorting"],
        answer: "Preaching",
      },
      {
        question: "The following are wrong motives for preaching except:",
        options: ["For an Occupation", "For Edification", "For Monetary gains"],
        answer: "For Edification",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The preaching of the Gospel is not with enticing words of man's wisdom but by the power of God.",
        options: ["True", "False", "Not sure"],
        answer: "True",
      },
      {
        question: "The following are types of sermons except:",
        options: ["Based on the Word", "Based on Topics", "Based on Trends"],
        answer: "Based on Trends",
      },
      {
        question: "The following are types of preaching except:",
        options: ["Reproof", "Critiquing", "Rebuke"],
        answer: "Critiquing",
      },
      {
        question: "The following are sermons based on doctrine except:",
        options: ["Soteriology", "Eschatology", "Lot, the backslidden Father"],
        answer: "Lot, the backslidden Father",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The act of worshipping, communing with the Holy Spirit, and spending time in the Word of God alone in one's private life is known as:",
        options: ["Public Worship", "Personal Devotion", "Temple Worship"],
        answer: "Personal Devotion",
      },
      {
        question:
          "A sermon is in three parts, including all the following except:",
        options: ["Excerpts", "The Introduction", "The Invitation"],
        answer: "Excerpts",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The preaching of the Gospel must be devoid of all distractions. A preacher of the Word must pay attention to what he/she wears, speaks, gesticulates, and speaks.",
        options: ["Not Necessarily", "True", "False"],
        answer: "Not Necessarily",
      },
      {
        question:
          "'Let your speech be always with grace, seasoned with salt, that ye may know how ye ought to answer every man.' Where can the above text be found?",
        options: [
          "Colossians 4 vs 2",
          "Colossians 4 vs 6",
          "Colossians 4 vs 8",
        ],
        answer: "Colossians 4 vs 6",
      },
      {
        question:
          "As a minister of the Gospel, the following should characterize your appearance: Simplicity, Neatness, and Spirituality.",
        options: ["False", "True", "Not Important"],
        answer: "True",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    title: "Church Pioneering and Church Dynamics",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          '"Christ is the Lord of the Church Planting and He has a vision for your new Church." The above principle describes:',
        options: [
          "The Mission Principle",
          "The Barnabas Principle",
          "The Boss Principle",
        ],
        answer: "The Boss Principle",
      },
      {
        question:
          '"God is Planting strong Local Churches and He\'s equipping the believers to walk in the Supernatural."',
        options: ["Not Necessarily", "False", "True"],
        answer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "In church planting, Prayer is important and the principle that is appropriate for prayerful planning is:",
        options: [
          "Leadership Principle",
          "The Magnet Principle",
          "The Nehemiah Principle",
        ],
        answer: "The Nehemiah Principle",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Attending to Organisational and administrative matters will protect and stabilise the new Church and enable it to grow in a healthy way.",
        options: ["False", "Not Necessarily", "True"],
        answer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "When people come to Christ, our job is to partner with the Holy Spirit in helping them grow. This is best described as:",
        options: [
          "Equipping System",
          "Spiritual Growth System",
          "The Assimilation System",
        ],
        answer: "Spiritual Growth System",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The following are causes of discouragement in ministry and church planting except:",
        options: [
          "Overworking and Exhaustion",
          "Praying and Studying the Word",
          "Clutter and Frustration",
        ],
        answer: "Praying and Studying the Word",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The process by which new converts and first-timers are made to find their place and get connected with the local church is called:",
        options: [
          "Welcoming Process",
          "Assimilation System",
          "Spiritual Growth System",
        ],
        answer: "Assimilation System",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The following are needed in assimilating newcomers into the church:",
        options: [
          "An official welcome",
          "Small Groups",
          "Bad First Impression",
        ],
        answer: "Bad First Impression",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The system that ensures that people are fed with the Word, care for each other, and feel cared for is:",
        options: [
          "Hospitality System",
          "Integration System",
          "Pastoral Care System",
        ],
        answer: "Pastoral Care System",
      },
      {
        question:
          '"People knowing and being known, loving and being loved, serving and being served, celebrating and being celebrated" is the most astute definition for:',
        options: ["Church Community", "Ministry Placement", "Good Leadership"],
        answer: "Church Community",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The principle that is applicable when dealing with difficult people is:",
        options: [
          "The Bridge Principle",
          "Mission Principle",
          "Power Principle",
        ],
        answer: "Mission Principle",
      },
      {
        question:
          "In dealing with difficult people and offenders, the following steps are instructed by the Lord Jesus Christ except:",
        options: [
          "Speaking with the offender privately",
          "Gossip the Offence and the Offender",
          "Take one or two witnesses to help",
        ],
        answer: "Gossip the Offence and the Offender",
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    title: "The Doctrine of Prayer",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "The best way to learn prayers is by praying.",
        options: ["False", "True", "Not Necessarily"],
        answer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          '"God will not do anything on the earth except men Prays." The proponent of the above quote is:',
        options: ["Smith Wigglesworth", "John Wesley", "Bob Jones"],
        answer: "John Wesley",
      },
      {
        question:
          '"...Lord teach us to pray, as John also taught his disciples" (Luke 11:1). This means that prayer is by precept and example.',
        options: ["True", "False", "None of the above"],
        answer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Jesus prayed all night in his earthly ministry. The significance of this gesture is that:",
        options: [
          "Prayer is extremely important",
          "Prayer is not as important",
          "None of the above",
        ],
        answer: "Prayer is extremely important",
      },
      {
        question: "The following are prayers we pray for ministers except:",
        options: [
          "Utterance and Boldness",
          "Preservation and Provision",
          "Filthy lucre",
        ],
        answer: "Filthy lucre",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The type of prayer we pray for saints as they keep walking with God and ministry according to Ephesians 6:18 is called:",
        options: ["Prayer of Faith", "Prayer of Need", "Supplications"],
        answer: "Supplications",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The confidence that we have in prayers is when we pray in the name of Jesus according to:",
        options: ["Our urgent Needs", "God's Will", "Church Needs"],
        answer: "God's Will",
      },
      {
        question: "Praying in other tongues is:",
        options: [
          "Praying in understanding",
          "Praying in the Spirit",
          "Praying amiss",
        ],
        answer: "Praying in the Spirit",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The way a believer edifies himself and builds up himself in his most holy faith in life and ministry is by praying:",
        options: [
          "Pauline prayers",
          "Praying in the Holy Ghost",
          "Prayer of Faith",
        ],
        answer: "Praying in the Holy Ghost",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Fasting and Prayers make one walk in God's Plan effectively.",
        options: ["True", "Not Necessarily", "True"],
        answer: "True",
      },
      {
        question: "Mark 11:23-24 best describes:",
        options: ["Intercession", "Prayer of Faith", "Prayer of Agreement"],
        answer: "Prayer of Faith",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The longer the prayers, the more effective the impact of the same.",
        options: ["True", "Not Necessarily", "False"],
        answer: "True",
      },
    ],
  },
];
